Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 8)
Could it be...
that you're interested in me?
What if I say yes?
What can you do?
I like intelligent and brave women.
Apart from my sister,
you can be considered...
the most outstanding woman in the world.
Today, in court,
I saw that you hate Situ Xian to the core.
Why is that?
Because he killed my sister.
I want him to pay for it a thousand times over.
What kind of person...
was your sister?
It's so cold.
Sis.
You clearly...
hate me so much.
Why don't you abandon me?
Shut up.
Our parents are dead now.
You're the last family member...
I have left in this world.
I won't give up on you.
Never.
Sis.
I am afflicted by several poisons.
If you take me with you,
you won't get out of Wandu Mountain.
No.
Without my permission,
you can't give up,
you can't die.
I'm going to find the Golden Silkworm to cure you.
If you close your eyes now,
I'll never forgive you.
Xiao Ren!
I found the Golden Silkworm!
You're saved.
Take it quickly.
Get lost!
All of you, get lost!
Go away!
Believe it or not,
I'll kill you all!
Come out!
If you want to hurt Xiao Ren,
you'll have to step over my dead body!
Come on!
I'm not afraid of you!
I won't let you...
hurt Xiao Ren!
We'd been through so much together.
I'd always thought,
as long as I'm alive,
as long as I'm alive in this world,
she would never be alone.
Who would have thought...
that she would die before me?
Your sister treated you so well.
She wouldn't want to see you sad.
I haven't taken revenge yet.
I don't have time to be sad.
My sister uprooted Situ Xian's weaponry supply.
He has no choice but to secretly manufacture weapons
with the Qiang people.
Now, he urgently needs military funds.
Your Lu family's assets...
I'm afraid...
he's determined to get them.
He wants my family's assets?
I'm overjoyed.
If he doesn't want them,
I'll have to find a way to make him want them.
Alright.
Do whatever you want.
- I'm here. - You'll protect me, right?
Don't be envious.
You have it too.
Get lost.
Shao Yao, come quickly.
The roast goose your master brought...
is really delicious.
It suits my taste.
Ms. Lu Zhao,
only the roast goose suits your taste?
What about the one who brought it?
Do you like him?
Your master...
possesses exceptional abilities...
and extraordinary courage.
He's a good partner.
Who wouldn't like him?
Miss Lu.
Master is a man of great character.
He's not only worth cooperating with,
but also someone to entrust your life to.
Don't you have...
any interest in him at all?
What kind of person he is has nothing to do with me.
I won't entrust my life...
to a man.
We're just using each other.
Chief.
Don't be sad.
Even if Miss Lu is using you,
I'm truly sincere about you.
Wait for me. Why are you walking so fast?
Miss Lu, Lord Liu is here.
He's waiting for you in the main hall.
Father.
Lu Zhao.
- Father. - Lu Zhao.
What brings you here?
I've come here...
to ask for a favor.
We're family. There's no need to be formal.
Just tell me.
Come on, have a seat.
Lu Zhao,
then I'll get straight to the point.
Okay.
Your aunt...
drowned to death.
It wasn't a peaceful end.
At the funeral,
her eldest daughter should carry...
the white banner for her peace.
But now,
Xue Er has fallen ill.
Only you can send her off.
Is this...
appropriate?
After all, I'm already married.
Don't worry.
I've already instructed everyone...
to keep the funeral simple.
I understand, Father.
Then I will...
do my filial duty...
for my aunt.
Your aunt must be able...
to rest in peace...
after seeing you come to send her off.
Yes.
Rou Er,
rest in peace.
I'll take good care of our daughter.
Your Highness,
we've offered the pear cakes...
and poured the sacrificial wine.
This funeral is complete.
Aunt,
pear signifies departure.
With the pear cake eaten,
and the farewell wine drunk,
may you rest in peace.
Lu Zhao,
you must finish this half of the pear cake...
for the ceremony to be complete.
Rou Er,
rest in peace.
No matter what sacrifice I have to make,
I'll do my best...
to protect Xue Er.
I'll find out who's behind Lu Zhao...
and send them all to hell,
to comfort your departed soul.
Aunt,
the road to hell is not easy.
Don't worry...
because I'll soon send someone to accompany you.
The funeral ceremony is complete!
There are bandits!
Master...
Hurry!
Pretend to be dead.
Pretend to be unconscious.
I am the Princecess of Chu.
Who sent you?
How dare you lay hands on me?
A princess?
On this mountain, I am the emperor!
You're pretty.
If you serve me well,
I'll make you the empress!
After her!
Don't run!
Get up.
Lu Zhao has a powerful ally...
behind her.
This way, I can lure out the person behind her.
Keep a close eye on the cliff.
When someone comes to save her,
force them to jump off the cliff.
Master.
There's Jishui Pond at the bottom of Fox Tail Cliff.
Even if they fall,
they might not die.
What if they escape during the chaos?
They can't escape.
I've already put...
the most potent love poison...
in Lu Zhao's pear cake.
Once they jump off the cliff,
report to Prince of Chu to search below the cliff.
Then, with the two of them alone in the wilderness,
in the throes of passion,
that's when we'll catch them red-handed.
Master, you're brilliant.
Why did you stop running?
One more step back,
and you'll be in the abyss.
How about you...
just be my wife?
How dare you!
How dare you kill my men?
Jump! Why aren't you jumping?
I'm going to make you all die!
- Let's fight our way out. - No.
Do you trust me?
Jump.
Shoot!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, something bad has happened.
Where's Lu Zhao?
Why are you the only one who rushed back?
Where's my wife?
The caravan encountered bandits on the roadside cliff.
Her Highness...
was cornered by the bandits...
and fell off the cliff.
How did you do your job?
I've heard that...
the Lu Clan Chief is on his way to the capital.
If Lu Zhao dies...
at this critical moment,
I'll kill your whole family!
Your Highness, please calm down.
I heard there's a pond at the bottom of the cliff.
Even if Her Highness falls, she'll be fine.
I request that Your Highness send men forthwith to search for her.
Pass on my orders at once.
Go down to Fox Tail Cliff...
and search for Lu Zhao.
If you can't find her,
bring your heads to me!
Yes, Your Highness.
What's wrong with you?
Why is she so hot?
She looks like she's been drugged.
Take off your wet clothes.
I'll light a fire for you.
You've been drugged with love poison.
It's the Spring Cage Lock.
How to detoxify?
As long as we...